moneynations.com 2019-07-06

# Bollywood Charcha

## **Privacy Policy**

We are grateful for your interest in moneynations services and privacy info. We do not imply our privacy on what you have posted or commented on our website. You are not asked to submit your personal information at all in order to browse <http://moneynations.com/>  you can surf this site without revealing any of your personal information as we do not ask it unless you are participating in some contest with us.

**Information we require-**

After providing your personal data you are not anonymous to us and hence you can take advantage of all activities like posting comments, enrolling for a contest etc. In case if you participate in a contest then you may be asked to submit personal data like your name, address, contact details, email address with the optional info like your location, age, personal and professional interests, gender, your experience with us and any feedback etc.

In case you connect with Moneynations.com through any social networking site we can store your personal information you have chosen to display in that networks. Further, in case you can send or receive personal messages to another user of Moneynations, we are allowed to record all messages that you send or receive.

Note: We respect our visitors/users rights and support “Right to be forgotten”. If you think you’ve ever shared your contact details with us & want us to remove that info, please contact us at

**What About IP addresses?**

We may use your personal information or data with your use of Moneynations in order to implement, prevent, investigate, identity theft, fraud, or multiple accounts to prevent making abusive comments. In order to get such information we may collect data like IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider), which browser you are using to visit <http://moneynations.com/> like Google Chrome plus we also capture your time taken to surf on <http://moneynations.com/> and the number of pages you went across.

Sharing and use of personal information-

Although we use industry’s best standard measures to protect your personal information but at the same time we cannot have control over the other users with whom you share your user profile.

We may use the user information:-

  * In order to improve our website
  * To improve our content and products information
  * To rectify the correct info or content given on the site, if any
  * To make our beloved readers participate in various contests, surveys etc.
  * However, we do not disclose your personal information to others without your approval or in the occurrence of some specific incidents:-
  * In order to take any action against suspected illegal activities/ violation against our terms and provisions
  * To enforce or imply terms and conditions and privacy policies
  * To protect our reputation, property and our rights/ rights of third party and personal safety of the users
  * We may also disclose personal information if it is required by the law because it is necessary to disclose such informations.
  * In the case we are transferring or selling the website to other company, user’s info will be transferred too. We may disclose non-identifiable data to third parties which don't include your name, email address or contact number.

**Cookies:**

When you use your browser in order to visit or surf any website usually small text files can take place in your computer as browser’s history or program data subfolders which are called as ‘Cookie’. A cookie can be of two types- one which expires when you close the browser and another is which stays on your computer until you delete them manually by following your browser help directions. So like another company our readers will get cookies by us or by companies which are running their ads on our website. Cookies can help us and advertisers to analyze and identify users on our website and it also helps us to serve content to match your preferences.

**Policy updation:**

In any case, if we make a change or update our privacy policy we make sure to inform you by posting on our page/website. The updated policies will also come to effect as soon as it is posted.
